const dayNineQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "……………………….is the sacred hadith that its meaning is entirely from Allah while the wordings are that of the Prophet Muhammad himself May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him).",
    options: [
      "Al hadithul Mahfuz",
      "Al hadithus Shadh",
      "Al hadithul Qudsi",
      "Al hadithul Ma’ruf",
      "Al hadithul Mashur",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Tadlis is of two types, they are …………… and ………….",
    options: [
      "Tadlis Sabiqah and Tadlis lahiqah",
      "Tadlis Shadh and Tadlis Gareeb",
      "Tadlis Sanad and Tadlis Matn",
      "Tadlis Sahih and Tadlis Da’eef",
      "Tadlis Isnad and Tadlis Shuyuk",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Sahih Bukhari comprises of how many Hadiths (Note: Including repetition)?",
    options: ["7653", "7563", "7635", "7536", "7663"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "……………………….is the narration that is reported in different ways.",
    options: [
      "Al Mudallas",
      "As Shadh",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Mudtarib",
      "Al Munkar",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Maqlub is divided into two, what are they?",
    options: [
      "Maqlubus Sabiqah and Maqlubu lahiqah",
      "Maqlubu Shadh and Maqlubu Gareeb",
      "Maqlubus Sanad and Maqlubu Matn",
      "Maqlubu Sahih and Maqlubu Da’eef",
      "Maqlubu Isnad and Maqlubu Shuyuk",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "……………………….is the narration by a lesser authority in opposition to a narration of a more reliable authority.",
    options: ["Al Mudallas", "As Shadh", "Al Mudraj", "Al Maodu’", "Al Munkar"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "………………………….is the narration that a reporter or more are omitted at the beginning of the Isnad.",
    options: [
      "Al Mu’allaq",
      "Al Maoquf",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munqati’",
      "Al Maqtu’",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "An authentic Hadith is divided into two. What are they?",
    options: [
      "Bukahri and Muslim",
      "Isnad and Matn",
      "Sahih lithatih and Sahih ligayrih",
      "Hadith Qudsi and Hadith Nabiy",
      "Sahih isnad and Sahih shuyuk",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………………………is the person whose specialization is on Science of Hadith; has knowledge of many narrations with the level of authority of their reporters, and he is synonymous to Hafiz according to some scholars.",
    options: ["Mufti", "Shaykul Islam", "Al Muhaddith", "Raawiy", "Faqeeh"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………… is a book of hadith that its hadiths are arranged according to each companion’s name.",
    options: ["As Sunan", "Al Jami’", "Al Musnad", "Al Mu’jam", "Al Mustadrak"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………is a hadith that two or more reporters were omitted in its Isnad consecutively.",
    options: [
      "Al Mu’dal",
      "Al Maoquf",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munqati’",
      "Al Maqtu’",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "…………….is a hadith that is not connected irrespective of the stage where a reporter is omitted.",
    options: [
      "Al Mu’dal",
      "Al Maoquf",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munqati’",
      "Al Maqtu’",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where two accepted hadiths controvert each other, the three stages of its treatment are……, ……and…...",
    options: [
      "Aljam’u, At Tarikh and At Tarjeeh",
      "Isnad, Matn and Taraf",
      "Sahih, Hassan and Da’eef",
      "Raawiy, Marwiy ‘anh and Riwayah",
      "Sahabah, Tabi’ and Tabi’u Tabi’in",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Whoever meets the Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) in a state of Iman and die as a Muslim is called……………….",
    options: [
      "Al Ansar",
      "Al Muhajirin",
      "As Shahid",
      "As Sahabiy",
      "At Tabi’",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Hadith Hassan (sound hadith) is divided into two, what are they?",
    options: [
      "Daud and Ibn Majah",
      "Isnad and Matn",
      "Hassan lithatih and Hassan ligayrih",
      "Hadith Qudsi and Hadith Nabiy",
      "Haassan isnad and Hassan shuyuk",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
];
export default dayNineQuestions;
